export const quizes = [
    {
      question: "A blood transfusion is when a person receives donated blood. Why are transfusions given?",
      option1: "To increase the amount of blood",
      option2: "To increase the blood's ability to carry oxygen",
      option3: "To decrease the risk of bleeding",
      option4: "All of the above",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Which parts of the blood can be transfused?",
      option1: "A. Whole blood",
      option2: "Platelets",
      option3: "Red blood cells",
      option4: "All of the above",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the minimum you should weigh to donate blood?",
      option1: "100 pounds",
      option2: "110 pounds",
      option3: "115 pounds",
      option4: "125 pounds",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "How often can a donor give blood?",
      option1: "At any time",
      option2: "Every 2 months",
      option3: "Every 3 months",
      option4: "Every 6 months",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "How much blood usually is donated at a time?",
      option1: "1 pint",
      option2: "2 pint",
      option3: "1 quart",
      option4: "2 quarts",
      ans: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What are the common risks of donating blood?",
      option1: "Contract common viruses",
      option2: "Bacterial infection",
      option3: "Low blood pressure",
      option4: "None of the above",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Donated blood undergoes screening for which diseases?",
      option1: "HIV (the virus that causes AIDS)",
      option2: "Viral hepatitis",
      option3: "Diabetes",
      option4: "Both A & B",
      ans: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Which agency regulates blood donation?",
      option1: "American Medical Association",
      option2: "U.S. Health and Human Services",
      option3: "FDA",
      option4: "American Red Cross",
      ans: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "An advisory panel of experts has suggested that anyone who received transfusions before March 1992 be screened for which of these diseases?",
      option1: "HIV",
      option2: "Hepatitis C",
      option3: "Mononucleosis",
      option4: "Leukemia",
      ans: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which is the most common blood type among Americans?",
      option1: " O positive",
      option2: " O negative",
      option3: "AB positive",
      option4: "AB negative",
      ans: 1,
    },
  ];